Dear all,

The PhD council at department of Statistics, Stockholm University would like to
invite you to participate the statistics study group for PhD students.



We tend
to organize it in an very informal way.

 Biweekly on Wednesday 10:30--11:30 (can be extended to 12:00 if needed)
   starting from September 05, 2012 at B705.

You are welcome to bring a topic to discuss which can be

 [1] a tinny question that you encountered in your research,
 [2] a paper you found interesting and would like to discuss with us,
 [3] a presentation of your ongoing paper, project, and
 [4] etc...

Please contact me (Feng Li <feng.li@stat.su.se>) ONE WEEK before the seminar in
the situations of [2] and [3].

Please feel free to spread this message to your friends.

And very importantly: Thanks to the support of the department, coffee and snacks will
be served during the seminars.


Warm welcome!

Feng Li, PhD student
PhD student seminar organiz
